This is the case of Mr. and Mrs. Sprank, who came all the way from Germany to The SCOAN,
for a healing touch from our Lord Jesus Christ.
This is T.B. Joshua praying for those in attendance at the prayer line that Sunday.
He turns to Mr. and Mrs. Sprank.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Immediately at the mention of the name "Jesus Christ", the evil spirit in Mr. Sprank begins to react.
Satan is a defeated foe and he knows it.
Try though he may, it is the vanquished that flee before the victors.
Jesus Christ has given overcoming victory to all who are truly born-again.
The evil spirit cannot stand the fire of God's holiness, and the light of His purity.
This is no ordinary battle, but spirit against spirit.
The evil spirit inside Mr. Sprank wants to fight back.
It is what the Bible calls "stiff opposition".
Greater is He who is in us than all the forces that can be arrayed against us.
Watch what is happening.
Bowing to the authority in the name of Jesus Christ.
All the way from Germany.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
But it is foolish to think that inferior can defeat superior.
If you talk what you believe, satan has to listen.
And we know that when we rise up in faith in Jesus' name, satan must bow.
T.B. Joshua continues to administer spirit deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ.
Satan is powerless in the face of God's armour and power.
This is the truth of the gospel of Jesus Christ, powerful to pull down every fortress of satan.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
The Holy Spirit affects our words.
He uses our words as the weapon to bring deliverance, salvation, and all of God's blessings.
This man's body shakes and trembles under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
There is a gentleman who came all the way from Germany, right now being set free.
The Bible says that Jesus Christ is the Master-Healer.
In the time of His earthly ministry He gave commands to evil spirits that kill, steal, and destroy
to leave the lives of their victims, and they obeyed.
As it was, so it is.
See what is happening.
This is the power of God at work.
While T.B. Joshua continues to pray, the demonic powers in Mr. Sprank begin to manifest,
as a part of the deliverance process.
There is more to life than meets the ordinary eyes.
Different parts, different animals I'm removing from his system.
Take note of the characteristics of those animals.
You can know the animal that walks like this.
Okay.
The SCOAN Prayer Line
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Still under the check and conduct of the Holy Spirit, T.B. Joshua approaches him, takes his hand
raises him to his feet and embraces him.
To God be the glory.
The man has been set free.
You are now free.
You possessed powers and you are delivered from these.
OK, these are generational curses.
Powers, reptiles and pythons.
To God be the glory.
Thank You, Jesus, I’m free. Finally, I’m free.
That's my husband.
What do you say?
He is my husband.
You must have been taking note of some strange powers.
I do.
How?
In his behaviour.
He is always very angry, over nothing.
He just gets angry.
In the night, you just see him wake up.
Yes, it is true.
And when he wakes up, you just wake up and you see him sitting down.
You begin to ask yourself, ‘Why is he sitting down?’
He does it sometimes.
That is the time he is operating with that kind of powers.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
That is the wife to the man that has just been delivered.
Having delivered Mr. Sprank, T.B. Joshua now prays for Mrs. Sprank in the power of the Holy Spirit,
to heal past hurts and enable them to build a happy Christian home together.
She rises to her feet completely free.
Glory be to God.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Thorsten Sprank, my age is 42 years. I come from Germany.
What was the problem you were having before?
I’ve had the feeling for several years that I have some negative spirits
which make me unbalanced and lacking energy.
I never really operate on the full level of my possibilities.
They also make me sometimes aggressive without a real reason.
So, I’ve felt uncomfortable in life with something trying to keep me down.
I came here for a solution.
My relationships have had a lot of conflict because of my anger.
This has all impacted my daily life because I don’t have enough energy for the things I'm doing.
You were privileged to be placed at the prayer line of The SCOAN.
What actually happened there, when you had an encounter with Jesus Christ,
through His anointed servant Prophet T.B. Joshua?
Can you explain what actually happened there?
When the man of God started praying for me, these negative forces became
very visible, with more presence than I have experienced before.
I became aggressive and thought I had to fight them, to keep them at distance,
so that they would not overwhelm me and take control.
So, I started fighting against them, which gave me the feeling that I can keep them at distance.
It was only after a while that I became aware again of the presence of the man of God.
I looked for his support to release me from these spirits.
That was when he directed me and I was forced several times to the floor, and he touched my back.
Every time he did that I felt a big relief that something was leaving my body and I came to peace.
My intention was not to fight against the man of God but rather the opposite -
against the darkness and negative forces, where they seem to have their source, their origin.
It was not my own will. It was a reaction as I was trying to fight for solution for myself as I did before,
but I came here to get the healing through Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Only after some time we connected to him to look for support.
It was an unintended reaction as I tried to find a solution for myself at the beginning.
Immediately after the prayer, I felt disoriented as if waking from a long deep sleep
but now I feel more balanced and at peace
with a strength inside, giving me support and guiding my life.
Are you still having that aggressive nature in you?
No, not anymore.
So, you are completely delivered from it?
Yes, I am delivered in Jesus' name. Amen.
I am Rebecca Sprank, I am 36 years old.
Everything he said is true. He gets very angry and irritated over nothing.
Because we always watch Emmanuel TV, he believed he would be delivered
by Prophet T.B. Joshua and I believed it so strongly because I’ve seen mighty miracles
that God has used him to do.
I know he’s God’s servant.
He is God's general.
At a point I told my husband I wanted to be out of the marriage,
that I was happier before I met him.
He said I should give him an opportunity to come here to be prayed for by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
That was why we made our trip all the way from Germany to come here.
I thank God so much because immediately the man of God prayed for him, there was a visible reaction.
One can see that the negative forces in him that made him not to be himself encountered a stronger power,
which is the Spirit of God and immediately there was a reaction.
Like he explained - he is free. I thank God, he is free.
There is power in Christ and this power is obviously present in Prophet T.B. Joshua.
It is not something anybody can dispute because what happened is a confirmation of the fact
that he is anointed for our generation.
I thank God that my husband is free.
Because ordinarily he wouldn't have...
Everything he explained is an indication that this man is God's general.
There is no doubt about it.
For me it is really Jesus Christ walking on earth through the man of God.
People looking for help or healing, before trying hospitals,
they should look for the real Healer, who is Jesus Christ.
I thank God for my healing and my promise to God is to sin no more
and I want to increase my involvement in the local church.
My promise to God is to continually talk about His goodness and to go and sin no more.
I pray with you that the Lord Almighty will grant you the grace to live above sin, in Jesus' name. Amen.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 18/07/2018 + Mel